





ITIL, Senior ICT Specialist seeking roles in Websphere Application Server, Websphere Portal Server, Websphere Process Server, Tivoli Directory Server, IBM DB2, Troubleshooting, IBM HTTP Server, System Administration, Java, J2Ee, Tomcat, Weblogic, Struts, Oracle

Total Experience: 16 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Pursuing Graduation]

Highest Degree: Not Pursuing Graduation [Not

Current Designation: ICT Specialist

Current Company: Information and eGovernment Authority

(IGA)

Current Location: Bahrain

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Delhi / NCR, United

Arab Emirates (UAE)

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: IT/Networking-Mgr
Industry: Defence/Government

Key Skills: ITIL, Senior ICT Specialist, Networking Manager, Websphere Application Server, Websphere Portal Server, Websphere Process Server, Tivoli Directory Server, IBM DB2, Troubleshooting, IBM HTTP Server, System Administration, Java, J2Ee, Tomcat, Weblogic, Struts, Oracle

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Over 15+ years of total IT experience with more than 13+ years of experience in systems implementation, migration, administration, installation, configuration and support of IBM WebSphere products such as WebSphere Portal Server (HCL), IBMWebSphere Application Server, IBMWebSphere Process Server / BPM, WebSphere Message Broker / IIB in a cluster topology and hands-on experience on IBMHTTP Server, IBMMQ, LDAP, IBMDB2, Tomcat, GIT, ANT and AWS.

Hands-on experience on installation and configuration of LDAP Server (IBM Tivoli Directory Server) and WebSphere Portal integration as well as configuring and implementing single sign on (SSO) and SSL

Good Exposure in AWS Cloud Computing (CloudWatch, EC2, ELB, VPC, CFT, Elastic Beanstalk, S3, IAM, AWS Auto Scaling)

Experience in monitoring tool IBM Tivoli Monitoring Tool / AppDynamics
Hands on experience on GIT / IBM Rational Clear Case for Version Con

Hands-on experience on GIT / IBM Rational ClearCase for Version Control / Source code management system/tools.

Work Experience

- Information and eGovernment Authority (IGA) as ICT Specialist Jul 2012 to Till Date
- * Senior ICT Specialist (December 2017 to till date)
- * Senior Computer System Administrator (July2012 to November 2017)
- Gulf Business Machine (GBM) as WebSphere Portal and WAS Administrator May 2011 to Dec 2011
- Prodapt Solutions Pvt. Ltd. as WebSphere Portal and WAS Administrator Jan 2007 to Mar 2011
- Instance Software Solutions as Software Engineer Sep 2004 to Jan 2007

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: Not Pursuing Graduation (Not Pursuing Graduation)

^ Back to Top

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
WINDOWS	
SUSE Linux	
Red Hat Linux	
WebSphere Application Server	
LDAP, DB2, JDBC	
Tomcat, AWS, GIT	
Clearcase, ANT	
IBMWEBSPHERE	
IBMHTTP Server	
IBMMESSAGE BROKER	
Tomcat Server	
EC2, ELB, VPC, CFT	
S3, IAM	
Java and J2EE	
MyEdipse	
MYSQL, DB2	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.